<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dynamic Movement Primitives on Daehyung&#39;s Homepage</title>
    <link>https://pidipidi.github.io/tags/dynamic-movement-primitives/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dynamic Movement Primitives on Daehyung&#39;s Homepage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Daehyung Park</copyright>
    <atom:link href="/tags/dynamic-movement-primitives/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Obstacle Avoidnace</title>
      <link>https://pidipidi.github.io/project/dmp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 22:46:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pidipidi.github.io/project/dmp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Robots in a human environment need to be compliant. This compliance requires that a pre-planed movement can be adapted to an obstacle that may be moving or appearing unexpectedly. Here, we present a general framework for movement generation and mid-flight adaptation to obstacles. For robust motion generation, Ijspeert et al developed the dynamic movement primitives, which represent a demonstrated movement with a differential equation. This equation allows adding a perturbing force without sacrificing stability. We extend this framework such that arbitrary movements in end-effector space can be represented - which was not possible before. Furthermore, we include obstacle avoidance by adding to the equation of motion a repellent force - a gradient of a potential field centered around the obstacle. In addition, this article studies the effect of different potential fields and shows how to avoid obstacle-link collisions within this framework. We demonstrate the abilities of our framework in simulations and with an anthropoid robot arm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Supervised Learning (Dynamic Movement Primitives)
Obstacle Avoidance by Potential Field Approach
7-DoF Redudant Manipulator
Null-Space Elbow Avoidance&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
